{
    "cards": [
        {
            "ID": 1,
            "Question": "origami",
            "Answer": "おりがみ；折り紙",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 2,
            "Question": "crane",
            "Answer": "つる；鶴",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 3,
            "Question": "to fold",
            "Answer": "おる；（紙を）折る；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 4,
            "Question": "to appear; seem",
            "Answer": "みえる；（〜に）見える；る",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 5,
            "Question": "to be different",
            "Answer": "かわっている；（〜が）変わっている；る",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 6,
            "Question": "triangle",
            "Answer": "さんかく；三角",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 7,
            "Question": "end; point; tip",
            "Answer": "さき；先",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 8,
            "Question": "to put together; fit in",
            "Answer": "あわせる；（〜を／に）合わせる；る",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 9,
            "Question": "to turn over; knock over; overturn",
            "Answer": "ひっくりかえす；（〜を）ひっくり返す；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 10,
            "Question": "line",
            "Answer": "せん；線",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 11,
            "Question": "to follow",
            "Answer": "そう；（〜に）沿う；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 12,
            "Question": "side",
            "Answer": "がわ；側",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 13,
            "Question": "to branch off; divide into; split",
            "Answer": "わかれる；（〜に）分かれる；る",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 14,
            "Question": "tail [animal]",
            "Answer": "しっぽ",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 15,
            "Question": "wing; feather",
            "Answer": "はね；羽",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 16,
            "Question": "center; middle",
            "Answer": "まんなか；真ん中",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 17,
            "Question": "to fold down; bend",
            "Answer": "まげる；（〜を）曲げる；る",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 18,
            "Question": "breath",
            "Answer": "いき；息",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 19,
            "Question": "to blow; play (fluent, etc.)",
            "Answer": "ふく；（〜を）吹く；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 20,
            "Question": "to be finished; be ready",
            "Answer": "できあがる；（〜が）出来上がる；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 21,
            "Question": "[conuter for birds/rabbits]",
            "Answer": "わ；羽",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 22,
            "Question": "to get well; be cured",
            "Answer": "なおる；（病気が）治る；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 23,
            "Question": "hospitalization",
            "Answer": "にゅういん；入院",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 24,
            "Question": "string; thread",
            "Answer": "いと；糸",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 25,
            "Question": "to tie; connect",
            "Answer": "（〜を）つなぐ；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 26,
            "Question": "atomic bomb",
            "Answer": "げんばく；原爆",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 27,
            "Question": "hospital room",
            "Answer": "びょうしつ；病室",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 28,
            "Question": "small [used for noun modifier]",
            "Answer": "ちいさ（な）；小さ（な）",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 29,
            "Question": "leaf",
            "Answer": "は；葉",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 30,
            "Question": "scissors",
            "Answer": "ハサミ；はさみ",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 31,
            "Question": "to hold between; sandwich",
            "Answer": "（〜を）はさむ；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 32,
            "Question": "shape; state of things; condition",
            "Answer": "じょうたい；状態",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 33,
            "Question": "corner",
            "Answer": "かど；角",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 34,
            "Question": "to get dry",
            "Answer": "かわく；（〜が）乾く；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 35,
            "Question": "a number of days",
            "Answer": "にっすう；日数",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 36,
            "Question": "glue",
            "Answer": "のり",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 37,
            "Question": "to stick; paste",
            "Answer": "はる；（〜に〜を）貼る；う",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 38,
            "Question": "handmade; homemade",
            "Answer": "てづくり；手作り",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        },
        {
            "ID": 39,
            "Question": "tissue (paper)",
            "Answer": "ティッシュ（ペーパー）",
            "Records": [
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    0
                ],
                [
                    "2024-12-04",
                    1
                ]
            ]
        }
    ]
}